ninkipal.com 2018-06-27

# Reviews

###  Privacy Statement

Thank you for Navigating through Ninkipal website and reviewing our privacy statement.  
Our privacy policy is plain and simple. We collect NO personal information, like names or addresses, when you visit our website. If you choose to provide that information to us, it's only used to fulfill your request for information.  
Please read this Privacy Statement carefully so that you understand what information we collect through our website and what we do with that information. This Privacy Statement applies only to information collected online through the NINKIPAL website and does not describe the ways in which we may collect or use information obtained offline or through any means other than our website. If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please Contact Us. The Information We Collect

Ninkipal Website does not automatically gather any specific personal information from you, such as your name, phone number or e-mail address. We would only obtain this type of information if you supply it by sending us an e-mail or registering as a member. Ninkipal does not normally use "cookies" to track how our visitors use this site or to determine sites previously visited. If cookies are in use and you have your cookies notification option activated on your browser the system will notify you before any cookies are used so that you may refuse them. (A "cookie" is a file that may be placed on your hard drive without your knowledge by a Web site to allow it to monitor your use of the site.) We will not give out any personal or business information to third parties, unless required to do so by law, or for the purpose of shipping and clearing the vehicle. We will not sell, give or exchange your information with any other business.

From time to time we may undertake to send you details of promotions or specials, however this will be done by us and no third party will have your information. Automatically Collected and Stored Information 

When users browse, read pages, or download information on Ninkipal Website, we automatically gather and store certain technical information about your visit. This information never identifies who you are. The information we collect and store about your visit is listed below:

#####  The Internet domain (for example, "Ycompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the web) from which you access our website;

#####  The type of browser (such as Firefox, Netscape, or Internet Explorer) and operating system (Windows, Unix) used to access our site;

#####  The date and time you access our site; and,

#####  The pages you visit.

This information is only used to help us make the site more useful for you. With this data, we learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We never track or record information about individuals and their visits. How Will You Use The Information That You Collect? We use this information to help us better understand your browsing and shopping requirements. Through this we believe that we can offer you more relevant and timely products and services and attempt to improve your browsing and shopping experience with us. The main uses of the data are:

#####  To process your order and administer your account (including debt tracing and collection and fraud prevention);

#####  To enable us to review, develop and improve the products, services, special offers and events that we offer;

#####  To provide access to future planned privileged areas of the website and provide additional information;

#####  To administer contests and competitions; and

#####  To keep you informed about new products.

Changes to these Privacy Statements The web is an evolving medium. If we need to change our privacy policy at some point in the future, we'll post the changes to this Privacy Statement on this website and update the reference to the effective date to reflect the date of the amendment. By visiting NINKIPAL CO.,LTD , you agree that your visit, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Statement.
